<resources>
    <string name="joke0">Q.Whats the difference between a tractor and a giraffe? A.One has hydraulics the other has highbollocks.</string>
    <string name="joke1">Q. What kind of band doesn't play music? A. A highbred.</string>
    <string name="joke2">Q. If one is single and two is a couple and three is a crowd, what is four and five? A. 9 (5+4)</string>
    <string name="joke3">Q. What do you get when you cross a parrot and a lion? A. I don't know, but when it talks you'd better listen.</string>
    <string name="joke4">Q. Why do giraffes have long necks? A. Because they have smelly feet.</string>
    <string name="joke5">Q. Why did the orange use suntan lotion? A. He started to peel.</string>
    <string name="joke6">Q. Where does an elephant go when he wants to lie down? A. Anywhere he pleases.</string>
    <string name="joke7">Q. What did the big chimney say to the little chimney? A. "You are too young to smoke."</string>
    <string name="joke8">Q. What did the fish say to the seashores? A. "Can I ride on you seashorse?"</string>
    <string name="joke9">Q. Why did Cinderella get kicked off the baseball team? A. Because she ran away from the ball.</string>
    <string name="joke10">Q. A man went to play golf for the day. He took his golf clubs and two pairs of pants. What were the extra pants for? A. In case he got a hole-in-one.</string>
    <string name="joke11">Q. Why didn't the skeleton cross the road? A. Because it had no guts.</string>
    <string name="joke12">Q. I have 3 heads, 5 legs, 7 arms and 444 fingers. What am I? A. A liar.</string>
    <string name="joke13">Q. What do you get when you cross an elephant with a kangaroo? A. Holes all over Australia.</string>
    <string name="joke14">Q. What goes ha, ha plonk? A. Someone laughing their head off.</string>
    <string name="joke15">Q. What do you get when you cross a duck with cheese? A. Cheese and quackers.</string>
    <string name="joke16">Q. What monster sits on the end of your finger? A. The bogie man.</string>
    <string name="joke17">Q. What did the computer screen say to the keyboard after it went for a ride? A. That was a harddrive.</string>
    <string name="joke18">Q. What is a pirate's favourite letter? A. R(Arrrrrggggh)</string>
    <string name="joke19">Q. Why did the cow jump over the moon? A. Because the farmer had cold hands.</string>
    <string name="joke20">Q. How do you make a tissue dance? A. Put a little boogie in it.</string>
    <string name="joke21">Q: How do you get a man to stop biting his nails? A: Make him wear shoes.</string>
    <string name="joke22">Q: Why do chicken coops have two doors? A: Because if it had four doors it's be a chicken sedan.</string>
    <string name="joke23">Q: What is the difference between a tick and a lawyer? A: A tick falls off you when you die.</string>
    <string name="joke24">Q: What's the definition of mixed emotions? A: When you see your mother-in-law backing off a cliff in your new car.</string>
    <string name="joke25">Q: What do call a lawyer with an IQ of 50? A: Your Honor.</string>
    <string name="joke26">Q: How do you know if a restaurant has a clown as a chef? A: When the food tastes funny</string>
    <string name="joke27">Q: Why do Farts stink? A: So that Deaf people can enjoy them too.</string>
    <string name="joke28">Q: Why did the Hedgehog cross the road? A: To see his Flat Mate.</string>
    <string name="joke29">Q: What do you call a Fish without an eye? A: A 'Fsh'!</string>
    <string name="joke30">Q: Why does it take 1 million sperm to fertilize one egg? A: They won't stop to ask directions.</string>
    <string name="joke31">Q: What's the difference between Big Foot and an intelligent man? A: Big Foot's been spotted several times.</string>
    <string name="joke32">Q: What do you call a handcuffed man? A: Trustworthy.</string>
    <string name="joke33">Q: What did the fish say when he hit a concrete wall? A: "Dam".</string>
    <string name="joke34">Q: Why is divorce so expensive? A: Because it's worth it.</string>
    <string name="joke35">Q. What is black, white and red all over? A. A skunk with nappy rash.</string>

    <string name="joke36">Q. Why did the man jump out of the window? A. He wanted to catch a butterfly.</string>
    <string name="joke37">Q. Why did the monkey put a piece of steak on his head? A. He thought he was a griller.</string>
    <string name="joke38">Q. What do you call a deer with no eyes? A. No eye deer.</string>
    <string name="joke39">Q. What do you call a deer with no eyes and no legs? A. Still no eye deer.</string>
    <string name="joke40">Q. Why was six afraid of seven? A. Because seven eight nine.</string>
    <string name="joke41">Q. Why did the dinosaur walk across the road? A. Because chickens were not invented yet.</string>
    <string name="joke42">Q. What has four wheels and flies? A. A rubbish truck.</string>
    <string name="joke43">Q. What's brown and sticky? A. A stick.</string>
    <string name="joke44">Q. When were vowels invented? A. When u and i were born.</string>
    <string name="joke45">Q. What's orange and sounds like a parrot? A. A carrot.</string>
    <string name="joke46">Q. What do you call a sheep with no head and legs? A. A fuzz ball.</string>
    <string name="joke47">Q. What do you call a fairy that hasn't bathed in a year? A. Stinkerbell.</string>
    <string name="joke48">Q. When is it a good time to eat a window? A. When it's jammed.</string>
</resources>